[SPEAKER_00]: Always like a little sleeping spot.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is a large sleeping area.
[SPEAKER_00]: All the footprints.
[SPEAKER_00]: They have the bathroom here, water.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll hold you, I'll hold you, I'll hold you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_00]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you have a headlamp?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like a waterfall here, when it rains.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, there's deer, lots of deer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, that's a big cave, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's about 20 meters there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: A classic secret cave behind a waterfall.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, there's a drop here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sunny, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good boy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go, go, go, go, go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go, go, go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Excellent boy.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, that's the ridge.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's where we went.
[SPEAKER_00]: Where we always go, yeah?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I know where we are.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, there's a bench here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, is that where we are?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that trail right down there.